{"question": "What is the application deadline for the winter semester for the program Aerospace - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "15.05. – 15.07.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/aerospace-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Chemical Engineering - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "6", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/chemical-engineering-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the winter semester for the program Biomedical Neuroscience - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "01.01. – 31.05.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/biomedical-neuroscience-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Engineering Science - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "6", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/engineering-science-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Medical Life Science and Technology (PhD-Program) - Doctorate Program?", "correct answer": "English", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/medical-life-science-and-technology-phd-program-promotion"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the winter semester for the program Pharmaceutical Bioprocess Engineering - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "15.05. – 15.09.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/pharmaceutical-bioprocess-engineering-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the summer semester for the program Electrical Engineering and Information Technology - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "01.10. – 30.11.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/electrical-engineering-and-information-technology-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Molecular Biotechnology - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/molecular-biotechnology-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Technology of Biogenic Resources - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "4", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/technology-of-biogenic-resources-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the winter semester for the program Finance and Information Management (FIM) - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "01.01. – 31.05.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/finance-and-information-management-fim-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the cost of the EMBA Tuition Fees for the program Executive MBA in Business & IT - Master of Business Administration (MBA)?", "correct answer": "39000 €", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/executive-mba-in-business-it-master-of-business-administration-mba"}
{"question": "For the program Vocational Education and Innovation - Master of Science (M.Sc.), what is the standard duration of studies expressed in number of semesters?", "correct answer": "5", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/vocational-education-and-innovation-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the winter semester for the Data & Society - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "01.04. – 31.05.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/data-and-society-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "For the Chemical Engineering - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program, what is the required language proficiency?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/chemical-engineering-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the minimum score required in TOEFL (Internet-Based Test) for the Integrated Circuit Design - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "88", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/integrated-circuit-design-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "At which TUM campus does the Sustainable Energy and Processes - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program take place?", "correct answer": "Straubing", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/sustainable-energy-and-processes-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What are the three areas of specialization offered in the Geodesy and Geoinformation - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "higher geodesy and satellite geodesy, photogrammetry, remote sensors and cartography, as well as geodesy, geoinformatics and land management", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/geodesy-and-geoinformation-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for admission to the Medical Engineering - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/medical-engineering-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Geophysics - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "4", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/geophysics"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the Political Science - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) program for the winter semester?", "correct answer": "15.05. – 15.07.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/political-science-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the Geodesy and Geoinformation - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/geodesy-and-geoinformation-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "Is proof of English language proficiency required for the Information Engineering (at TUM Campus Heilbronn) - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "No", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/information-engineering-at-tum-campus-heilbronn-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Lehramt an Realschulen – Unterrichtsfach Sport - State Exam Program?", "correct answer": "7", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/lehramt-an-realschulen-unterrichtsfach-sport-staatsexamen"}
{"question": "What are the application periods for the Sustainable Management and Technology - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program for the winter and summer semesters?", "correct answer": "Winter semester: 01.04. – 31.05. Summer semester: 01.11. – 30.11.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/sustainable-management-and-technology-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the Politics & Technology - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program for the winter semester?", "correct answer": "01.04. – 31.05.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/politics-technology-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the Biology - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program for the winter semester?", "correct answer": "01.01. – 31.05.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/biology-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Data Engineering and Analytics - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "4", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/data-engineering-and-analytics-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the Business Education I - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/business-education-i-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Vocational Education Agriculture (Teaching at Vocational Schools) - Master of Education (M.Ed.)?", "correct answer": "4", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/vocational-education-agriculture-teaching-at-vocational-schools-master-of-education-med"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the winter semester for the program Information Systems - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "15.05. – 15.07.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/information-systems-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Chemistry - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "6", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/chemistry-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Green Electronics - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "English", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/green-electronics-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the winter semester for the program Computational Science and Engineering (CSE) - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "01.02. – 31.05", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/computational-science-and-engineering-cse-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Biochemistry - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "4", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/biochemistry-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the winter semester for the program Agrosystem Sciences - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "01.04. – 31.05.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/agrosystem-sciences-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Chemical Biotechnology - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "English", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/chemical-biotechnology-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the summer semester for the program studium MINT (Certificate) - Certificate?", "correct answer": "15.11. – 15.01.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/studium-mint-certificate-zertifikat"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Industrial Biotechnology - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/industrial-biotechnology-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Teaching at Academic Secondary Schools – Scientific Education - Master of Education (M.Ed.)?", "correct answer": "4", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/teaching-at-academic-secondary-schools-scientific-education-master-of-education-med"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Physics (Nuclear, Particle and Astrophysics) - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/physics-nuclear-particle-and-astrophysics-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Biomass Technology - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "4", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/biomass-technology-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the winter semester for the program Risk and Safety - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "01.01. – 31.05.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/risk-and-safety"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Engineering and Materials Science - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "6", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/engineering-and-materials-science-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Vocational Education Health and Health Care Science (Teaching at Vocational Schools) - Bachelor of Education (B.Ed.)?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/vocational-education-health-and-health-care-science-teaching-at-vocational-schools-bachelor-of-education-bed"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Neuroengineering - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "English", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/neuroengineering-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Geomaterials and Geochemistry - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "4", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/geomaterials-and-geochemistry-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the winter semester for the program Forest and Wood Science - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "01.04.2022 – 31.05.2022", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/forest-and-wood-science-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Food Chemistry - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/food-chemistry-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Vocational Education Electrical Engineering and Information Technology (Teaching at Vocational Schools) - Bachelor of Education (B.Ed.)?", "correct answer": "6", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/vocational-education-electrical-engineering-and-information-technology-teaching-at-vocational-schools-bachelor-of-education-bed"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Lehramt an Mittelschulen – Didaktikfach Sport - State Exam Program?", "correct answer": "5", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/lehramt-an-mittelschulen-didaktikfach-sport-staatsexamen-1"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Automotive Engineering - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "German or English", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/automotive-engineering-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Mathematics - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/mathematics-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Urbanism – Urban and Landscape Studies and Design - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/urbanism-urban-and-landscape-studies-and-design-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Food Technology - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "6", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/food-technology-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Management and Data Science - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "English", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/management-and-data-science"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program ESPACE – Earth Oriented Space Science and Technology - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "4", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/espace-earth-oriented-space-science-and-technology-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Bioinformatics - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/bioinformatics-master-of-science-msc-1"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Environmental Engineering - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "6", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/environmental-engineering-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Agricultural and Horticultural Sciences - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "6", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/agricultural-and-horticultural-sciences-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the Management (am Campus Heilbronn) - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program for the winter semester?", "correct answer": "01.04. – 31.05.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/management-main-location-heilbronn-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the English language proficiency requirement for the Executive MBA in Innovation and Business Creation - Master of Business Administration (MBA) program?", "correct answer": "skills will be assess during the admission process, no test results required", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/executive-mba-in-innovation-and-business-creation-master-of-business-administration-mba"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Mechatronics, Robotics and Biomechanical Engineering - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "4", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/mechatronics-robotics-and-biomechanical-engineering"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the Vocational Education Agriculture (Teaching at Vocational Schools) - Bachelor of Education (B.Ed.) program?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/vocational-education-agriculture-teaching-at-vocational-schools-bachelor-of-education-bed"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the Responsibility in Science, Engineering and Technology (RESET) - Master of Arts (M.A.) program for the winter semester?", "correct answer": "01.01. – 31.05.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/responsibility-in-science-engineering-and-technology-reset-master-of-arts-ma"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the Informatics - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program for the summer semester?", "correct answer": "01.10. – 30.11.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/informatics-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Mechanical Engineering - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "4", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/mechanical-engineering-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program AgriFood Economics, Policy and Regulation - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "English", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/agrifood-economics-policy-and-regulation"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Vocational Education Nutrition and Home Economics (Teaching at Vocational Schools) - Master of Education (M.Ed.)?", "correct answer": "4", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/vocational-education-nutrition-and-home-economics-teaching-at-vocational-schools-master-of-education-med"}
{"question": "What are the required language proficiencies for the program Robotics, Cognition, Intelligence - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "German and English", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/robotics-cognition-intelligence-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Electronics and Data Engineering - Bachelor of Engineering (B.Eng.)?", "correct answer": "8", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/electronics-and-data-engineering-bachelor-of-engineering-beng"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Biogenic Materials - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/biogenic-materials-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Radiation Biology - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "4", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/radiation-biology-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Brewing and Beverage Technology - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/brewing-and-beverage-technology-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Lehramt an Grundschulen und Mittelschulen – Unterrichtsfach Sport - State Exam Program?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/lehramt-an-grundschulen-und-mittelschulen-unterrichtsfach-sport-staatsexamen"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Life Sciences Biology - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "6", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/life-sciences-biology-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Technology of Biogenic Resources - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/technology-of-biogenic-resources-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the program Development, Production and Management in Mechanical Engineering - Master of Science (M.Sc.)?", "correct answer": "4", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/development-production-and-management-in-mechanical-engineering-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What are the application periods for the Management and Technology - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "winter semester: 01.04. – 31.05. Summer semester: 01.11. – 30.11.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/management-and-technology-tum-bwl-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "How many ECTS credits do students obtain per semester in the Cartography - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "30", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/cartography-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Teaching at Academic Secondary Schools – Scientific Education - Bachelor of Education (B.Ed.)?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/teaching-at-academic-secondary-schools-scientific-education-bachelor-of-education-bed"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Mechanical Engineering - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "6", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/mechanical-engineering-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "In the Management and Technology (am Campus Heilbronn) - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) program, what percentage of the courses are management courses?", "correct answer": "70", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/management-and-technology-tum-bwl-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "How many ECTS credits are required for the Architecture - Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) program?", "correct answer": "240", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/architecture-bachelor-of-arts-ba"}
{"question": "In which city is the Aerospace Engineering - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program conducted?", "correct answer": "61 Nanyang Drive, Singapore", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/aerospace-engineering-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the duration of the Master's thesis in the Food Technology - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "1 semester (4th semester)", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/food-technology-and-biotechnology-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the Vocational Education Nutrition and Home Economics (Teaching at Vocational Schools) - Bachelor of Education (B.Ed.) program?", "correct answer": "15.05. – 15.07.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/vocational-education-nutrition-and-home-economics-teaching-at-vocational-schools-bachelor-of-education-bed"}
{"question": "What is the total credit points (ECTS) for the Management and Technology - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "120", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/management-and-technology-tum-bwl-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for Lehramt an Mittelschulen – Didaktikfach Sport - State Exam Program?", "correct answer": "5", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/lehramt-an-mittelschulen-didaktikfach-sport-staatsexamen-1"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the program Lehramt an beruflichen Schulen – Masterstudiengang Berufliche Bildung Integriert - Master of Education (M.Ed.)?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/lehramt-an-beruflichen-schulen-masterstudiengang-berufliche-bildung-integriert-master-of-education-med"}
{"question": "Is the Logistics Engineering and Management - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program taught in English?", "correct answer": "Yes", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/logistics-engineering-and-management-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Mechanical Engineering - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "6", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/mechanical-engineering-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the Information Systems - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/information-systems-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the language of instruction for the Microelectronics and Chip Design - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "English", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/microelectronics-and-chip-design-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Geosciences - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "6", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/geosciences-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Information Engineering (at TUM Campus Heilbronn) - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "6", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/information-engineering-at-tum-campus-heilbronn-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the Responsibility in Science, Engineering and Technology (RESET) - Master of Arts (M.A.) program?", "correct answer": "English", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/responsibility-in-science-engineering-and-technology-reset-master-of-arts-ma"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Brewing and Beverage Technology - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "6", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/brewing-and-beverage-technology-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What are the application periods for the Sustainable Management and Technology - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "Winter semester: 01.04. – 31.05. Summer semester: 01.11. – 30.11.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/sustainable-management-and-technology-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the Sustainable Resource Management - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "01.01. – 31.05.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/sustainable-resource-management-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Computational Mechanics - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "4", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/computational-mechanics-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the required language proficiency for the Forest and Wood Science - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "German", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/forest-and-wood-science-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the Microelectronics and Chip Design - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "01.02. – 31.05.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/microelectronics-and-chip-design-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the tuition fees for the Executive MBA in Innovation and Business Creation - Master of Business Administration (MBA) program?", "correct answer": "39000 €", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/executive-mba-in-innovation-and-business-creation-master-of-business-administration-mba"}
{"question": "Where is the Industrial Chemistry - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "Singapore", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/industrial-chemistry-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Technology of Biogenic Resources - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "4", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/technology-of-biogenic-resources-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the Pharmaceutical Bioprocess Engineering - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "15.05. – 15.09.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/pharmaceutical-bioprocess-engineering-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Medicine (Clinical Work) - State Exam Program?", "correct answer": "12", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/medicine-clinical-work-staatsexamen"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Integrated Circuit Design - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "4", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/integrated-circuit-design-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the Environmental Engineering - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) program for the winter semester?", "correct answer": "15.05. – 15.07.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/environmental-engineering-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Bioinformatics - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "6", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/bioinformatics-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the Politics & Technology - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program for the winter semester?", "correct answer": "01.04. – 31.05.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/politics-technology-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the Physics (Applied and Engineering Physics) - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program for the summer semester?", "correct answer": "01.09. – 30.11.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/physics-applied-and-engineering-physics-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the Civil Engineering - Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) program for the winter semester?", "correct answer": "15.05. – 15.07.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/civil-engineering-bachelor-of-science-bsc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Vocational Education and Innovation - Master of Science (M.Sc.) program?", "correct answer": "5", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/vocational-education-and-innovation-master-of-science-msc"}
{"question": "What is the standard duration of studies for the Teaching at Academic Secondary Schools – Scientific Education - Bachelor of Education (B.Ed.) program?", "correct answer": "6", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/teaching-at-academic-secondary-schools-scientific-education-bachelor-of-education-bed"}
{"question": "What is the application period for the Psychology with Specialization in School Psychology for Teacher Certification at Vocational Schools (bachelor's supplementary degree program component) - Other program for the winter semester?", "correct answer": "15.05. – 15.07.", "source": "https://www.tum.de/en/studies/degree-programs/detail/psychology-with-specialization-in-school-psychology-for-teacher-certification-at-vocational-schools-bachelors-supplementary-degree-program-component-sonstiges"}
